gadgets.in 2010-06-22

# Buy privacy policy at Gadgets.in - an Online Shopping Store! Electronic Gadgets & Gift items in India

On Gadgets.in, privacy issues are a high priority for us and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**Policy Coverage:**

This Privacy Policy covers Gadgets.in's treatment of personally identifiable information that Gadgets.in collects when you are on the Gadgets.in site, and when you use Gadgets.in's services. This policy also covers Gadgets.in's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Gadgets.in's business partner's share with Gadgets.in. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Gadgets.in does not own or control, or to people that Gadgets.in does not employ or manage.

**Information collected by Gadgets.in:**

Gadgets.in collects personally identifiable information when you send us content for publication in the form of a sign-up. We may ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, pincode, occupation, industry, personal interests etc. Once you have sent us this information and sign in to our services, you are given a unique ‘Gadgets.in ID' and are not anonymous to us anymore.

**Use of information by Gadgets.in:**

Gadgets.in uses information for two general purposes: to customize the content you see and to contact you about specials and new products. Gadgets.in WILL NOT sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. Gadgets.in may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when:

We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested and given your consent;

We have to cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities;

When we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights and related property of Gadgets.in and that of its visitors;

Gadgets.in uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure.

Gadgets.in may amend this policy from time to time. We understand that our number one assett shop | pricing policy is our ‘members' and we will never knowingly do anything to harm the trust you have bestowed on us.

We use any information voluntarily you give us to enhance your experience in our site, which is to provide you with interactive or personalized elements on the sites and to better prepare future content based on your interests. We aggregate this tracking information to determine which areas of our site members like and don't like based on traffic to those areas.
